What's up for the weekend, Joe?
周末干什么,Joe?
We'll probably go sailing.
我们可能去航海.
The weather should be good.
天气应该会不错.
At least that's what the weather report said.
至少天气预报是这么说的.
How's the boat?
那船怎么样了?
She needs a little work...
船需要一点工作...
a little work, a lot of cash.
一点工作,一大笔钱.
Ugh, this coffee's got sugar in it.
Ugh,这杯咖啡里有糖.
This one must be yours.
这杯一定是你的.
It gets expensive, doesn't it?
它变得很贵,不是吗?
Please.
拜托.
Marie reminds me the entire time we're on the boat.
我们在船上时  Marie一直都这么提醒我.
She says it's just a hole in the water you throw money into.
她说那就是水上的一个洞  你往里边扔钱.
I'm thinking of getting a smaller one,
我正在考虑买艘小点儿的,
Richard, a one-man sailboat.
Richard,一艘单人帆船.
Ugh. This one's got sugar in it, too.
Ugh.这杯里也有糖.
You want it?
你要吗?
No, thanks. Do you want this milk?
不,谢谢.你要牛奶吗?
Sure.
当然.
Beth used to take riding lessons.
Beth以前上骑术课.
That wasn't cheap.
那可不便宜.
I was relieved when she got tired of it.
我松了一口气当她厌倦时.
This isn't a ham sandwich.
这不是火腿三明治.
I'm not sure what it is.
不知道是什么.
Egg salad.
鸡蛋沙拉.
What's that one?
那是什么?
Pastrami. Wrong order.
五香烟熏牛肉.送错外卖了.
Wrong order.
送错了.
The last couple of years, we've been skiing.
过去几年里,我们常去滑雪.
We go to Stowe Mountain in Vermont.
我们去Vermont的Stowe山.
Is that the one with the two mountains and all the trails?
是不是有两座山、许多小路的那个地方?
Yep. Downhill skiing.
Yep.顺山坡滑雪.
We can't pick an inexpensive sport, can we?
我们就不能选一种便宜的运动, 对吗?
Is there one?
有吗?
Skinny-dipping.
裸泳.
That would be a summer activity.
那会是夏天的活动.
Pretty much.
基本上是.